[
  {
    "question": "Which boy band included Nick Carter?",
    "correctAnswer": "Backstreet Boys",
    "options": [
      "Boyzone",
      "NSYNC",
      "One Direction",
      "Backstreet Boys"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the popular name for little baked sausages wrapped in rashers of streaky bacon?",
    "correctAnswer": "Pigs in blankets",
    "options": [
      "Little weiners",
      "Swine rolls",
      "Porkos",
      "Pigs in blankets"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Polish astronomer has craters on the moon and Mars named after him?",
    "correctAnswer": "Copernicus",
    "options": [
      "Copernicus",
      "Hubble",
      "Galileo",
      "Kepler"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country is the city of Zagreb?",
    "correctAnswer": "Croatia",
    "options": [
      "Germany",
      "Croatia",
      "Luxembourg",
      "Estonia"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In phonetics, which of these is an example of a plosive sound?",
    "correctAnswer": "The t in 'train'",
    "options": [
      "The m in 'mother'",
      "The n in 'no'",
      "The y in 'yellow'",
      "The t in 'train'"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What French word means 'to feel sorry for' and means 'street' in France?",
    "correctAnswer": "Rue",
    "options": [
      "Avenue",
      "Rue",
      "Boulevard",
      "Lane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actress has appeared in films including Murder on the Orient Express and Counterpart?",
    "correctAnswer": "Jacqueline Bisset",
    "options": [
      "Jacqueline Bisset",
      "Mila Kunis",
      "Sophia Loren",
      "Hilary Duff"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the abbreviation for the polymer that carries genetic instructions for living cells?",
    "correctAnswer": "DNA",
    "options": [
      "DNA",
      "ATP",
      "COD",
      "GCI"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these quotes is from the film '2001: A Space Odyssey'?",
    "correctAnswer": "\"Open the pod bay doors, please, HAL.\"",
    "options": [
      "\"Forget it, Jake, it's Chinatown.\"",
      "\"I love lamp.\"",
      "\"Iâ€™m the guy who does his job. You must be the other guy.\"",
      "\"Open the pod bay doors, please, HAL.\""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name given to parts of the world where the population lives significantly longer than average?",
    "correctAnswer": "Blue zones",
    "options": [
      "Health spots",
      "Longevity lands",
      "Octogenarial regions",
      "Blue zones"
    ]
  }
]